(Penny:)Uh, you know,
I-I'm not really
around that much.
(Penny:)Amy knows much more
than I do.
(Leonard:)I don't think you have
anything to worry about.
(Leonard:)Raj is a terrific guy,
loyal to a fault.
(Howard:)Yeah. He still has
an AOL address.
(Zack:)I see what you're saying.
(Zack:)She's not so great.
(Raj:)Don't listen to him.
(Raj:)He says crazy things
all the time.
(Raj:)Uh, watch. Marco.
Polo!
(Raj:)So, uh, what are
you guys talking about?
(Claire:)Your friends were
just telling me about
(Claire:)all the other girls
you're dating.
(Raj:)Why would you do that?
(Raj:)I specifically asked you
not to do that.
(Howard:)We didn't.
(Amy:)You just did.
(Zack:)Wow. Maybe none of
you guys are smart.